Caffè Lena collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Subseries 7: Dick Kavanaugh collection
    - Sub-subseries 1: Music
      - Anita Silvert (1 of 2), July 10, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR312)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0057.
      - Anita Silvert (2 of 2), July 10, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR311)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0056.
      - New Performer Showcase: Jeff Gonzales, Robert Dinardo, Dierdre Bollinger, The Landfill Mountain Boys (Mike Slick, Howard Jack, Chuck Munsen) (1 of 2), July 26, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR350)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0037.
      - New Performer Showcase: Jeff Gonzales, Robert Dinardo, Dierdre Bollinger, The Landfill Mountain Boys (Mike Slick, Howard Jack, Chuck Munsen) (2 of 2), July 26, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR351)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0038.
      - St. Regis String Band (1 of 2), July 31, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR313)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0058.
      - St. Regis String Band (2 of 2), July 31, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR314)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0059.
      - Cathy Winter (1 of 2), August 1, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR256)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0001.
      - Cathy Winter (2 of 2), August 1, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR257)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0002. Side B is blank.
      - Charles Pace (1 of 2), August 7, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR258)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0003.
      - Charles Pace (2 of 2), August 7, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR259)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0004. Side B is blank.
      - Artie Traum with friends: Amy and Leslie, Sredni Vollmer (2 of 2), August 14, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR260)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0005. Part 1 of 2 is missing.
      - Pierce Pettis (1 of 2), August 15, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR262)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0007.
      - Pierce Pettis (2 of 2), August 15, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR263)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0008.
      - Christine Lavin (1 of 2), August 21, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR184)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0041.
      - Christine Lavin (2 of 2), August 21, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR185)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0042.
      - Rosalie Sorrels (1 of 2), August 28, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR217)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0019.
      - Rosalie Sorrels (2 of 2), August 28, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR218)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0020.
      - Dave Van Ronk, August 1987, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR261)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0006. The engineer's notes give the date as August 1991.
      - Anne Hills (1 of 2), Elizabeth Suedos, September 5, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR199)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0001.
      - Anne Hills (2 of 2), September 5, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR200)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0002. Side B is blank.
      - Tom Chapin (1 of 3), September 11, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR271)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0016.
      - Tom Chapin (2 of 3), September 11, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR272)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0017.
      - Tom Chapin (3 of 3), September 11, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR270)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0015.
      - Peggy Atwood live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), September 18, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR273)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0018.
      - Peggy Atwood live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), September 18, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR274)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0019. Side B is blank.
      - New Performer Showcase: Terri Roben, Chris Hewitt, Jem Moore and Ariane Lydon (Passages), Steve Key and Frank Fusco (1 of 2), September 20, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR348)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0035.
      - New Performer Showcase: Terri Roben, Chris Hewitt, Jem Moore and Ariane Lydon (Passages), Steve Key and Frank Fusco (2 of 2), September 20, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR349)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0036.
      - Steve Gillette live at Caffè Lena, September 25, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR295)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0040.
      - Ian Macintosh live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2?), October 3, 1987 [?], 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR275)
        The notes regarding SR275-277 are unclear as to their relationship. Original item ID: DK B5 0020.
      - Ian Macintosh live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), October 2, 1987 [?], 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR276)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0021.
      - Ian Macintosh live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), October 2-3, 1987, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR277)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0022.
      - Mary McCaslin and Jim Ringer (1 of 2), October 11, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR179)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0036.
      - Mary McCaslin and Jim Ringer (2 of 2), October 11, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR178)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0035. Side B may be a rehearsal.
      - Jerry Rasmussen live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), October 17, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR280)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0025.
      - Jerry Rasmussen live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), October 17, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR281)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0026. Side B is blank.
      - Robin and Linda Williams (1 of 2), October 18, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR168)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0025.
      - Robin and Linda Williams (2 of 2), October 18, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR169)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0026.
      - New Performer Showcase: Wayne Wiseman, Denise Jordan Finley, Steve Kovacik (1 of 2), October 25 or 26, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR352)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0039.
      - New Performer Showcase: Wayne Wiseman, Denise Jordan Finley, Steve Kovacik (2 of 2), October 25 or 26, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR353)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0040.
      - Charlie King live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), November 14, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR283)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0028
      - Charlie King live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), November 14, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR284)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0029. Side B is blank.
      - Magpie (Terry Leonino and Greg Artzner) (1 of 2), December 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR339)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0025.
      - Magpie (Terry Leonino and Greg Artzner) (2 of 2), December 4, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR340)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0026.
      - Garnet Rogers (1 of 2), December 6, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR338)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0024.
      - Garnet Rogers (2 of 2), December 6, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR337)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0023.
      - Lena celebrates the holidays: old fashioned evening (1 of 2), December 15, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR333)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0019.
      - Lena celebrates the holidays: old fashioned evening (2 of 2), December 15, 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR334)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0020. Side B is blank.
      - Dana Lyons (1 of 2), December 27, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR326)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0012.
      - Dana Lyons (2 of 2), December 27, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR327)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0013.
      - Dave Van Ronk - New Years Eve (1 of 2), December 31, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR198)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0055.
      - Dave Van Ronk - New Years Eve (2 of 2), December 31, 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR319)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0005.
      - Don Heynie and Cheryl Samuel (1 of 2), December 1987, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR267)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0012.
      - Don Heynie and Cheryl Samuel (2 of 2), December 1987, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR266)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0011. Side B is blank. The engineer's notes give the date as December 11, 1981.
      - Guy Van Duser (1 of 2), January 30, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR331)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0017.
      - Guy Van Duser (2 of 2), January 30, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR332)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0018. Side B is blank.
      - New Performer Showcase: Cross Baugh (Kathy Daly, Jerome Benton, Gary Moon), Sara Dylan, Heather and Sue Pottor (1 of 2), February 14, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR357)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0044.
      - New Performer Showcase: Cross Baugh (Kathy Daly, Jerome Benton, Gary Moon), Sara Dylan, Heather and Sue Pottor (2 of 2), February 14, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR356)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0043.
      - In loving memory of Michelle Tondreau, February 28, 1988, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR229)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0031. Performers include Dave Utter.
      - Chris Proctor, February 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR362)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0049.
      - Dan Hicks and the Acoustic Warriors, Maryann Kreitlow (1 of 3), March 6, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR162)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0019.
      - Dan Hicks and the Acoustic Warriors, Maryann Kreitlow (2 of 3), March 6, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR163)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0020.
      - Dan Hicks and the Acoustic Warriors, Maryann Kreitlow (3 of 3), March 6, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR164)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0021.
      - Jem Moore and Ariane Lydon ("Passages") (1 of 2), March 11, 1988, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR227)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0029.
      - Jem Moore and Ariane Lydon ("Passages") (2 of 2), March 11, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR228)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0030. Side B is blank.
      - Shay's Rebellion: John O'Connor, Janet Stecher, Susan Lewis (1 of 2), March 12, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR363)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0050.
      - Shay's Rebellion: John O'Connor, Janet Stecher, Susan Lewis (2 of 2), March 12, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR364)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0051. Side B is blank.
      - Scott Alarik (1 of 2), March 19, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR365)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0052.
      - Scott Alarik (2 of 2), March 19, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR366)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0053. Side B is blank.
      - Poncho with Tony Markellis and Frank Orsini (1 of 2), April 1, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR182)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0039.
      - Poncho with Tony Markellis and Frank Orsini (2 of 2), April 1, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR183)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0040.
      - New Performer Showcase: Marie Gillard, Sandy Bradshaw, Space Pies (Peter Taormina), Bill Cormier with Jem Moore (1 of 2), April 3, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR354)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0041. Side B is described as "broken."
      - New Performer Showcase: Marie Gillard, Maria Gillard, Sandy Bradshaw, Steve Gillette (2 of 2), April 3, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR355)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0042. Side B is described as "broken."
      - Jacqui McDonald and Bridie, guest set by Judy Gorman-Jacobs (1 of 2), April 8, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR324)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0010.
      - Jacqui McDonald and Bridie, guest set by Judy Gorman-Jacobs (2 of 2), April 8, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR325)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0011.
      - Andrew Calhoun (1 of 2), April 23, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR264)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0009.
      - Andrew Calhoun (2 of 2), April 23, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR265)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0010. Side B is blank.
      - Bob Franke (1 of 2), April 29, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR221)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0023.
      - Bob Franke (2 of 2), April 29, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR222)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0024. Side B is blank.
      - Amy Freiden and Leslie Ritter (1 of 2), April 30, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR195)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0052.
      - Amy Freiden and Leslie Ritter (2 of 2), April 30, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR196)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0053. Side B is blank.
      - Steve Key and Frank Fusco (1 of 2), May 14, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR210)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0012.
      - Steve Key and Frank Fusco (2 of 2), May 14, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR211)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0013. Side B is blank.
      - Townes Van Zandt, July 31, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR167)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0024.
      - Caffè Lena 28th Anniversary: Michael Cooney (1 of 2), May 20, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR358)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0045. Duet with Lena Spencer at the end of Side B.
      - Caffè Lena 28th Anniversary: Michael Cooney (2 of 2), May 20, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR359)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0046.
      - New Performer Showcase: Krystalblu (Dave Pechette, Terry Pechette, Decky Wright), Thelma Lumpkin, Rich Rose (1 of 2), May 15, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR344)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0031.
      - New Performer Showcase: Krystalblu (Dave Pechette, Terry Pechette, Decky Wright), Thelma Lumpkin, Rich Rose (2 of 2), May 15, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR345)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0032.
      - Caffè Lena 28th Anniversary: Michael Cooney (1 of 2), May 21, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR360)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0047.
      - Caffè Lena 28th Anniversary: Michael Cooney (2 of 2), May 21, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR361)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0048.
      - Headin' South, and Doherty, Riley, and Grant live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), July 5, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR306)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0051.
      - Headin' South live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), July 5, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR305)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0050.
      - The Whippersnappers (George Wilson, Frank Orsini, Peter Davis) (1 of 2), July 8, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR328)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0014.
      - The Whippersnappers (George Wilson, Frank Orsini, Peter Davis) (2 of 2), July 8, 1988, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR329)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0015. Side B is blank.
      - Tom Chapin; Danny Quinn (opening act) (1 of 3), July 19, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR368)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0055.
      - Tom Chapin (2 of 3), August 19, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR369)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0056.
      - Tom Chapin (3 of 3), August 19, 1988, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR370)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0057.
      - Dave Van Ronk: instructional guitar recording, possibly 1988 or 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR144)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0001. SR034-SR036 may be three parts in a series.
      - Dave Van Ronk: instructional guitar recording, possibly 1988 or 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR145)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0002. SR034-SR036 may be three parts in a series.
      - Dave Van Ronk: instructional guitar recording, possibly 1988 or 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR146)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0003. SR034-SR036 may be three parts in a series.
      - Gamble Rogers (1 of 2), January 10, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR316)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0002.
      - Gamble Rogers (2 of 2), January 10, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR315)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0001. Side B is blank.
      - Garnet Rogers (1 of 2), January 14, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR335)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0021. Guest set by Alien Folk Life after intermission.
      - Garnet Rogers (2 of 2), January 14, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR336)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0022.
      - Bill Staines at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), January 20, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR302)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0047.
      - Bill Staines at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), January 20, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR301)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0046.
      - Rosalie Sorrels (1 of 2), February 25, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR219)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0021.
      - Rosalie Sorrels (2 of 2), February 25, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR220)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0022. Side A is blank.
      - Vassar Clements, May 14, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR214)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0016.
      - Vassar Clements, May 14, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR215)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0017. Side A has the same content as Side A of SR215. Side B is blank.
      - Bob Franke (2 of 2), May 14, 1989, 1 sound cassette (60 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR216)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0018. Side B is blank. Documentation indicates this recording may be either Vassar Clements or Bob Franke.
      - Greg Brown (1 of 2), July 21, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR341)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0027.
      - Greg Brown (2 of 2), July 21, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR342)
        Original item ID: DK B6 0028.
      - Rory Block (1 of 2), September 22, 1989, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR207)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0009.
      - Rory Block (2 of 2), September 22, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR208)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0010.
      - Terri Roben and Maria Caccavio live at Caffè Lena (1 of 2), September 23, 1989, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR286)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0031.
      - Terri Roben and Maria Caccavio live at Caffè Lena (2 of 2), September 23, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR287)
        Original item ID: DK B5 0032. Side B is blank.
      - Townes Van Zandt (1 of 2), September 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR165)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0022.
      - Townes Van Zandt (2 of 2), September 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR166)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0023. Half of tape comprised of unrelated record and radio dubs.
      - Chris Smither, October 7, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR240)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0042.
      - Paul Geremia (1 of 2), November 11, 1989, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR173)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0030.
      - Paul Geremia (2 of 2), November 11, 1989, 1 sound cassette (100 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR174)
        Original item ID: DK B3 0031.
      - Series of voice mails for Lena or Dick, November 22, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette: analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR113)
        Original item ID: DK B1 0009. Side A is blank.
      - Utah Phillips (1 of 2), November 24, 1989, 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR202)
        Original item ID: DK B4 0004.
      - Utah Phillips (2 of 2), November 24, 1989, on 1 side of 1 sound cassette (90 min.): analog, stereo. (Item id AFC 2009/035: SR201)